var loreQList = [
    {
      Question: "What is the name of the missing Yaksha featured in Interlude: Perilous Trail?",
      A: "Marchosius",
      B: "Guhua",
      C: "Rex Lapis",
      D: "Bosacius",
      ANS: "D",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which of the following weapons does the Traveler use during Archon Quest Cutscenes?",
      A: "Favonius Sword",
      B: "Dull Blade",
      C: "Aquila Favonia",
      D: "Harbinger of Dawn",
      ANS: "B",
    },
    {
      Question: "In the Inazuma Archon Quest Act III, which character saves the Traveler from Scaramouche?",
      A: "Yae Miko",
      B: "Kazuha",
      C: "Raiden Shogun",
      D: "Tartaglia",
      ANS: "A",
    },
    {
      Question: "The Favonius Cavalry Captain, Kaeya, is said to have orgins from",
      A: "Celestia",
      B: "Fontaine",
      C: "Inazuma",
      D: "Khaenri'ah",
      ANS: "D",
    },
    {
      Question: "Paimon has given an 'ugly nickname' to every character listed EXCEPT",
      A: "Venti",
      B: "Arataki Itto",
      C: "Raiden Shogun",
      D: "Xingqiu",
      ANS: "C",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which of the following is NOT a title that the Raiden Shogun holds?",
      A: "Beelzebul",
      B: "Eternal Excellency",
      C: "Kunikuzushi",
      D: "Ei",
      ANS: "C",
    },
    {
      Question: "In which quest does Shenhe make her first appearance into the story?",
      A: "The Crane Returns on the Wind",
      B: "A New Star Approaches",
      C: "Sea of Clouds, Sea of People",
      D: "Farewell, Archaic Lord",
      ANS: "A",
    },
    {
      Question: "This character was a member of the Watatsumi Army who was killed during the Inazuma Archon Quest due to Aging",
      A: "Nathan",
      B: "Imaizumi",
      C: "Enomoto",
      D: "Teppei",
      ANS: "D",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which of the following Archon Quests does NOT feature the Traveler's twin?",
      A: "For a Tomorrow Without Tears",
      B: "A Soul Set Apart",
      C: "Memories of Inteyvat",
      D: "Omnipresence Over Mortals",
      ANS: "D",
    },
    {
      Question: "Paimon's infamous, 'hehe te nandayo' JP line is said in which quests in the Prologue?",
      A: "The Outlander Who Caught the Wind",
      B: "State of the Holy Lyre der Himmel",
      C: "Sparks Amongst the Pages",
      D: "Calm Before the Storm",
      ANS: "B",
    },
  ];
